# **Benjamin Gomez**

# Full Stack Web Developer

1907 Hamilton Ave | Austin, Texas 78702 LinkedIn | <u>linkedin.com/in/benjamin-a-gomez</u> GitHub | <u>github.com/bennygo3</u> (602) 471-5651 | <u>gobecodeme@gmail.com</u>

#### **About Me**

I am a Full Stack Developer with experience designing, developing and deploying full stack applications. I enjoy the process and challenges of conceiving an idea for a new application and bringing that idea to life.

I am also a licensed paramedic that has years of experience working in a highly demanding environment. That said, I look forward to continuing on in the demanding environment of software development.

Dog dad to two and husband of one.

# **Education**

The Coding Bootcamp at UT Austin | GPA 4.0

Austin, Texas

Certificate of Completion from UT Austin - Full Stack Web Developer - March 2022

Austin Community College | GPA 3.3

Austin, Texas

Level Two Certificate in Emergency Medical Services – Paramedic – May 2017 Level One certificate in Emergency Medical Services - EMT Intermediate – May 2016

Horizon High School

Phoenix, Arizona High School Diploma

#### **Skills**

Programming languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React.js, Express.js, Node.js, jQuery, Bootstrap.

Database technologies: MongoDB, MySQL, JSON.

Other technologies: Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Object Oriented Programming, Database Theory, Command Line and Git.

#### **Certifications and Licensure**

Full Stack Web Developer - March 2022
Licensed Paramedic - July 2017
Emergency Medical Technician - May 2015
ACLS Provider - June 2016
PHTLS - April 2016
FEMA Introduction To Hazardous Materials - April 2016
FEMA Radiological Emergency Management - March 2016
FEMA Introduction To Incident Command System - April 2015
FEMA National Incident Management System - April 2015

# **Experience**

#### Ambulance | Paramedic, 500+ Clinical Hours

I have served as an EMT, EMT Intermediate and a Paramedic for over 500 clinical hours with San Marcos-Hays County EMS, Williamson County EMS and Austin-Travis County EMS, most recently supervised by Captain Jason Beggs for Austin-Travis County.

My senior semester required 240 clinical hours on an ambulance in either Austin-Travis County or Williamson County and I was fortunate enough to have my internship at Medic 2 in Austin-Travis County. The sheer amount of call volume that was responded to has prepared me to adequately deal with a plethora of situations.

#### Hospital | EMT Intermediate, 80+ Clinical Hours

I have served as an EMT and an EMT Intermediate for over 80 clinical hours with UMC Brackenridge, South Austin Medical Center, Seton Medical Center Austin and Seton Northwest Hospital, supervised by various hospital staff. I was able to successfully hone a number of skills thanks to the permission to practice from the aforementioned hospitals, including numerous airway management, venipuncture, medicine administration and communication procedures.

#### Private Practice | July 2017 - January 2021

Primary Caregiver, Medical Coordinator for James "Jim Bob" Robert Moffett. I coordinated care for Mr Moffett with the help of various physicians, nurses and other healthcare related individuals. I gained experience managing and maintaining: airways, tracheostomies, gastrostomies tubes, central lines, urinary catheters, and nephrostomy tubes. Along with the medical responsibilities of the job, I aided Mr Moffett with his finanes, business endeavors and anything else he needed me to do.

#### Other Work Experience

Member Services, Barton Creek Resort | May 2013 – June 2017 This role required me to develop numerous business and personal relationships with various members of Barton Creek Country Club. I balanced customer-service oriented professional interaction with the golf course's guests and the physical labor required to keep the carts, range, and grounds ready for play.

Guest Services, TPC Scottsdale | September 2005-April 2013

TPC Scottsdale was my first place of employment. The standards the company set helped positively shape my development from an adolescent to a young adult. I learned how to interact in a professional yet friendly manner with guests, coworkers and visitors.

## **Awards**

## 2016 St. David's Neal Kocurek ACC Scholarship Recipient

I was fortunate enough to be considered for and awarded the 2016 St. David's Neal Kocurek Scholarship which allowed me to further my focus as a student and realize my opportunity of becoming a medical professional.

## 2005 Arizona 5A varsity football

First team all region. My senior year of football I was statistically ranked top five in the state of Arizona for receiving yards and touchdowns. Yes, I refuse to omit this from my resume.